<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<data>
<!--51E67C9184F6439595409B46040FC572--><AD_MODULE>
<!--51E67C9184F6439595409B46040FC572-->  <AD_MODULE_ID><![CDATA[51E67C9184F6439595409B46040FC572]]></AD_MODULE_ID>
<!--51E67C9184F6439595409B46040FC572-->  <AD_CLIENT_ID><![CDATA[0]]></AD_CLIENT_ID>
<!--51E67C9184F6439595409B46040FC572-->  <AD_ORG_ID><![CDATA[0]]></AD_ORG_ID>
<!--51E67C9184F6439595409B46040FC572-->  <ISACTIVE><![CDATA[Y]]></ISACTIVE>
<!--51E67C9184F6439595409B46040FC572-->  <NAME><![CDATA[Main UI API]]></NAME>
<!--51E67C9184F6439595409B46040FC572-->  <VERSION><![CDATA[0.2.0]]></VERSION>
<!--51E67C9184F6439595409B46040FC572-->  <DESCRIPTION><![CDATA[Core metadata provider module for the new Etendo UI ecosystem. Delivers essential backend APIs that enable dynamic rendering of windows, tabs, fields, and components in the modern React-based interface. Handles entity definitions, field properties, layout]]></DESCRIPTION>
<!--51E67C9184F6439595409B46040FC572-->  <HELP><![CDATA[This module serves as the foundational metadata backbone for Etendo's next-generation user interface architecture. It provides comprehensive REST APIs that expose window metadata, tab structures, field definitions, business process configurations, and authentication services required by the new React-based frontend.

KEY FEATURES:
- Dynamic Window Metadata: Delivers complete window definitions including tabs, fields, references, and layout information
- Authentication Management: Implements token-based authentication system for secure API access
- Real-time Data Synchronization: Ensures frontend components stay synchronized with backend metadata changes  
- Field Configuration APIs: Exposes field properties, validation rules, display logic, and user interface rendering hints
- Business Process Integration: Provides metadata for processes, parameters, and workflow definitions
- Multi-language Support: Handles internationalization metadata for labels, help text, and field descriptions
- Security Integration: Manages role-based access control and field-level security configurations

DEPENDENCIES:
Requires Etendo Core [25.1.0,25.3.0], metadata.template 0.2.0, etendorx 3.3.0, OpenAPI Implementation 1.1.0, and Secure Web Services 1.3.4.

CONFIGURATION:
Set authentication.class=com.etendoerp.metadata.auth.AuthenticationManager in Openbravo.properties for proper token authentication with the new UI frontend.

This module is essential for the modern Etendo UI experience and should not be disabled if using the new React-based interface components.]]></HELP>
<!--51E67C9184F6439595409B46040FC572-->  <TYPE><![CDATA[M]]></TYPE>
<!--51E67C9184F6439595409B46040FC572-->  <JAVAPACKAGE><![CDATA[com.etendoerp.metadata]]></JAVAPACKAGE>
<!--51E67C9184F6439595409B46040FC572-->  <ISTRANSLATIONREQUIRED><![CDATA[N]]></ISTRANSLATIONREQUIRED>
<!--51E67C9184F6439595409B46040FC572-->  <AD_LANGUAGE><![CDATA[en_US]]></AD_LANGUAGE>
<!--51E67C9184F6439595409B46040FC572-->  <HASCHARTOFACCOUNTS><![CDATA[N]]></HASCHARTOFACCOUNTS>
<!--51E67C9184F6439595409B46040FC572-->  <ISTRANSLATIONMODULE><![CDATA[N]]></ISTRANSLATIONMODULE>
<!--51E67C9184F6439595409B46040FC572-->  <HASREFERENCEDATA><![CDATA[Y]]></HASREFERENCEDATA>
<!--51E67C9184F6439595409B46040FC572-->  <ISCOMMERCIAL><![CDATA[N]]></ISCOMMERCIAL>
<!--51E67C9184F6439595409B46040FC572-->  <ISTRIALALLOWED><![CDATA[N]]></ISTRIALALLOWED>
<!--51E67C9184F6439595409B46040FC572-->  <EM_ETRX_ISREACT><![CDATA[N]]></EM_ETRX_ISREACT>
<!--51E67C9184F6439595409B46040FC572--></AD_MODULE>

</data>
